Encode By MaNuDiL @ SilverRG
Every time we men are blamed that we are liars,
cheaters and dishonest.
Whereas the truth is that we poor men...
...are victims of a very big conspiracy.
Right from the first lesson in school...
...we are wrongly taught and lied to.
We are mis-taught.
Where we are taught that A stands for apple.
B for ball.
C for cat.
Our eyes open when we come to this great place known as COLLEGE.
After coming here we find out that...
A does not stand for Apple but in fact A stands for...
Similarly, B does not stand for Ball but in fact B stands for...
And do you know what C stands for? C stands for...
I am sure they got the point.
Right?
So basically, during these last few days of college...
we want to tell the future generation that, college is a place...
where we study the real A B C whole heartedly.
With true dedication and with our full body.
And we try that after all our efforts and hard work,
we definitely get an F.
Applause.
Go boys, go and practice.
Come on. Come on.
I have done so many experiments in Miss Rose's chemistry class...
but I repent that I couldn't do any experiment with her.
Meet...
Hi Meet...
Bye Meet.
Oh crap, Marlo.
How are you my cheeseballs?
I miss you, I love you.
Oh God. This carrom-board Marlow is again following me.
Poor girl has been following you with her coconut of love since years!
Just once put your straw and drink from it.
You idiot She is not a coconut!
She is a lemon.
Then have lemon water.
You both stop your coconut and lemon water!
There's a fruit salad waiting there for us.
Let's go.
You're like the light You're like a sugar syrup
The world has reached the Moon
While you're afraid to even come on the terrace
Love sustains the world While you're afraid to even express your love
O cruel one! Either give me your heart or kill me
You're like the light You're like a sugar syrup
Your intoxicating like a Margarita
Drinking you gives a different kind of high
You're hot You're like a shot of fun
Shower your fun on us too
You're a sweet girl You're like a bottle of neat alcohol
Give a sip or two to the thirsty
Open the whisky, pour the soda Who gives a damn about the world
O cruel one! Either give me your heart or kill me
My heart is getting restless It's getting grilled by your breath
Today is exhilarating and we're so near to our destination
Today I am in full mood, My queen!
You know it So do I... that
Youth never comes back again
Tear the pillow, tear the bed sheet Let's rock the bed tonight
O cruel one! Either give me your heart or kill me
You're like the light You're like a sugar syrup
Today is the last day for ABC...
and henceforth I will not stand...
What?
In this campus.
But before leaving, I will read her A B C till F.
Never fear when Hardik is here.
Why did you hit me?
Because all crime is a kind of disease..
...and should be treated as such...
Mahatma Gandhi...
It means every crime is a disease and curing it is necessary.
And now I will cure your disease for the next five years.
Who are you to cure me?
Robert Pareira.
Your new principal.
I am sorry, sir. I am a good student, sir.
I am sorry,
I am sorry, please forgive me.
With such pride you put a cover over her umbrella.
Now even I want to see
if you are really telling the truth or fooling that girl.
No sir.
This is known as, fine words butter no parsnips.
Henceforth, if any student...
...is seen flirting with any female student...
he will be tied to this tree, naked, just like this boy.
And where the offence is, let the great axe fall.
It means,
when required, punishment needs to be administered for wrongs done.
Thank God, the new Principal came on our last day here.
Just think,
if he was here during our year then what would've happened?
Yes.
We escaped.
Poor students! Their next five years in college will be heck.
But even after leaving college...
...our life will still be like college life!
One big party.
Drink it, please!
Take this hand out and put this in your mouth.
Why are you not drinking?
I gave you one work and you cannot do that also properly.
If Pappu is not drinking milk, how is it my mistake?
Did you shake it properly?
Yes Mamta, I have shaken it properly.
Anyways ever since Pappu's birth...
...I have become an expert in shaking it.
Give it to me.
It is so hot!
Do you want to burn my baby's mouth? no wonder he is not drinking.
Wait I will cool the milk.
Yes, go.
You cannot do anything properly.
I wish I had used a condom that night.
Keep quiet! How much will you cry?
Hello.
Where are you?
Ever since you've become a father you are nowhere to be found.
What can I tell you.
The day you will become a father...
you will know the pleasure of having a son.
Well you are very lucky.
Anyways are we meeting Prem tonight?
Yes, we have to pick up Prem from his bank.
But will you be able to leave office so early?
Of course I will.
This is the benefit of having your wife as your boss in the office.
She is the boss but I rule.
Bye.
Where is madam?
She is in her boss's cabin, as always.
It is just so...
It's so hot.
So cute.
Sir, it has grown so much since the last time I saw it.
Have you noticed, it gets so excited seeing you.
Sir, I wish that I could play with it everyday.
I just want to swallow it.
Sir, have a banana.
Sir, now I understood why madam is more suck cessful than you.
Naughty! If you like it so much, it could be yours, forever.
No, Meet will never agree.
No my lady, you are mistaken.
He hasn't seen it yet.
Once he sees it, he will fall in love with it.
I'm telling you, he just love it.
What did you do? Have you gone mad?
You were playing with a dog!
Yes.
Oh...f...
You! I mean you dog...
Why did you kick me?
Sir, I...
Sir, it's your banana's mistake.
It is my banana's mistake! - Yes.
You eat bananas and throw their peels all over the place.
I slipped and you got kicked.
Why did you enter my cabin?
I have some urgent work. I have to leave early.
Is it some official work?
No, personal.
One minute. I can't sanction leave for your personal work.
But baby... - Mr Meet,
this is an office, not your house.
Here, I am neither your baby nor your wife. I'm your boss.
Do you get it?
Now you can leave. - Out.
And take this with you.
Out. - Out.
Got a banana.
I don't know what they think of themselves.
They think I am a slave.
They won't grant me leave!
I just want to know if that slacker is in the office or not.
I hope so.
He is working.
He is working, thank God!
Nice.
Sex, twice a day.
You've to write, male or female, not number of times.
Fill up the form properly. Bloody show off.
Sext... Next...
What are you looking at uncle?
Hands up.
No one will move from their place.
You fool, put your hands up.
Why are you hitting me honey? I am doing it.
If anyone moves from their place, I will shoot them.
Take the cash.
Put all the cash in this bag.
Hurry up! - Yes.
Did anyone see who robbed the bank?
Yes, I have seen. You robbed the bank.
Is that so?
Yes.
Father.
Did you see who robbed the bank?
No I haven't seen but my wife has seen everything.
Is that so? You too have seen everything!
Thank you sir.
Problem solved.
Hurry up! Put all the cash inside.
Sit straight.
Don't try to act smart or I will shoot you.
Hurry up!
Oh God!
Who rang the alarm?
Leave the money. The police will be here. Run!
Guys, they have gone.
And we have come.
Mr. Prem, how are you feeling after stopping this bank robbery?
I cannot share my feelings with you.
I have to go.
Mr. Prem, one more question.
If you ask me one more question, my feelings will touch the ceiling.
I have to go.
But Mr. Prem...
Prem, what about our boy's night out?
Forget the boy's night out, I want to go in.
In?
I am very happy today.
What you did today has made the entire Chawla family proud.
Sit here. That was nothing.
You will know what you should be truly proud of, today...
my darling Tulsi. You are looking so juicy.
Tulsi, I need you in the kitchen.
I have to go, mom-in-law is calling me to make dal.
And I have to make rice too for father-in-law.
Here this Chawla is ready to ride on you
and you are worried about the rice.
I am sorry. I will come back immediately.
No!
Mom, you take rest. I will do it.
Okay.
Come.
The dal is ready and bread is also ready.
But now I cannot stay away from you anymore.
Come to me my chicken, Come to me
Tulsi, come and teach Chhotu.
What do you have to teach Chhotu?
Tomorrow is Chhotu's biology exam.
His grades were low in the previous test.
It's the rule of gravity, what goes up must come down.
Nothing can stay up for long.
Do you understand?
I have to go.
I will come back soon.
No, no, no.
You go, I will teach him.
Thank you.
Come.
Come my chicken.
I'm done teaching him.
Due to this family, I've forgotten your biology.
Now it's enough. I don't care who calls, you will not go.
Because I have a sexy surprise for you.
Don't go anywhere.
I will come back right away.
What is sister-in-law's cat doing here?
Come Pussy, come here.
Surprise!
Oh God!
Leave me. - Leave him!
Leave me.
Help help!
Leave him.
No.
Look at Nanga Gang's horrific act.
They have terrorized this country!
The members of this gang enter people's houses.
They enter their bedroom, take off their clothes...
and rape the sleeping women throughout the night.
And disappear in morning.
For more details about this gang...
...keep watching this channel on your TV...
if you care about your sister, daughter and wife.
Where is my wife?
Hello.
Yes Meet, tell me.
Unnati, where are you?
I am in my boss's house.
This is the fifth time in this week
that you went to your boss's house for a meeting after office hours.
What is going on?
What can I do?
Work is work.
I will be late.
Bye.
Hello...
She disconnected the call!
Boss...DK.
More than a boss he looks like the leader of Nanga gang to me.
Today I will catch them red-handed.
What a car!
He is earning so much!
He bought a new BMW!
I wish this BMW was mine.
My wife is a cheat.
She is cheating on me.
You are pouring petrol on my life.
See what I pour in your car.
BMW...
Hello.
Meet, where are you?
I am...
I have good news for you.
Boss has given me a surprise.
He is very happy with my work and so,
he has gifted me a brand new BMW.
I am coming home in the car We both will go for a long drive.
Okay, bye.
BMW!
Don't cry.
Everything will be fine.
Nothing will be fine, dad.
Don't say that.
Sir, what do you think? Can we save it?
We can save it but I don't think that he will be able to stand again.
She, not he.
My pussy is a female.
What did my cat do to you?
She always let you play with her Pussy.
If something happens to her pussy...
I will never forgive you.
Darling.
Everyone is concerned about Pussy!
No one is concerned about what the cat did!
What are you doing?
Even the pets are having sex.
Pappu, don't cry so much.
Go to sleep.
What happened to my baby?
Why are you crying?
Yeah! I have become taller.
I am a disco dancer.
Did Pappu go to sleep?
Yes.
Very good.
I haven't been able to enjoy because of Pappu.
But tonight, I will enjoy.
No.
Aren't you ashamed of talking like this in front of Pappu?
Was Pappu downloaded from Google?
Pappu came into this world because of all this.
I've waited for a long time.
Please allow me to proceed.
Please.
Okay, I will go and freshen up.
Okay.
Oh my!
Who is there?
Who are you?
Do I look like Salman Khan?
I am a thief. I have come here to rob.
Did you get today's date only?
Should I have taken an appointment?
Lower your voice.
Why? - Pappu will wake up.
After so long I got some time to be with my wife.
Get out!
Shall I wake up Pappu?
Do one thing. - What?
Take whatever you want without making any noise.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
Go. - Thank you.
Listen... - What?
Take him along with you.
I am a thief,
not running an orphanage to take this child along with me.
We will meet again. All the best.
Again?
Baby, I am here.
Oh God, I missed you so much.
Tonight, its just going to be the two of us. No one else.
Oh God, Pappu...
Pappu, oh God.
May I come in Doctor?
Come in.
Please sit.
What is your problem?
Doctor, give me some medicine to avoid pregnancy.
Pregnancy...
Take this condom.
Anyways it is of no use to me.
Should I have this with milk or water?
With a banana!
Have it with a banana.
Yes, because alone, it is of no use.
Thank you doctor.
Have fun.
I will. Thank you doctor.
You scared me.
What are you and Pappu doing here?
I came here to tell you that there has been a theft in the house.
I know. - What?
What?
How do you know?
You just told me that there was a theft in the house.
Let's lodge a complaint with the police.
Complaint...
you are concerned about Pappu the whole day!
If you had taken care of the house and me...
there wouldn't have been any thefts.
Hello.
Mr. Amar, I am speaking from Sluts.
Can we talk later?
No, you misunderstood me.
I mean,
Shri Lalchand University of Technology and Science. SLUTS in short.
Today the world uses BBM language, so in short form.
What is it?
To celebrate our college's 25th anniversary...
we are organizing a reunion week.
You and your family are invited to join us in a week-long celebration.
Wow! That's amazing!
This means, a week-long opportunity to enjoy college life once again!
Yes. So are you coming?
I will definitely come.
I love SLUTS. - What?
SLUTS. SLUTS.
Confirm.
Baby, I got a call from my college. There is reunion next week.
We will have lots of fun.
We will get a break from work and also,
get to spend time with each other.
Meet, I am very upset.
I will kill whoever did this to my car.
Don't curse him so much.
If I catch hold of him...
By the way,
next week I have to go to Turkey with my boss to attend a meeting.
A big deal has to be finalized.
So I can't come.
What do you mean? Why can't you come?
Next week Pappu has to get his vaccinations.
Get it cancelled. We will get it done after two weeks.
We cannot cancel the appointment.
Mom has chest congestion from last one week.
We have got this appointment with great difficulty.
Have you taken the responsibility of the entire family?
Brother and sister-in-law are also there.
Sister-in-law has gone to meet her parents along with pussy.
And your brother is too busy at work.
That means her job is more important to her than me!
Pappu! Pappu! Pappu! I am fed up with Pappu.
My Tulsi is for everyone except me.
Her father named her Mamta and she is taking her name too seriously.
Yes. - Yes.
Tell me one thing.
Why do wives forget the Kama sutra after marriage?
The families are not so joint even in Suraj Barjatya's movies.
As soon as the day comes to an end,
heroine indicates the hero to meet her alone.
But my wife says, I will go and come back right away.
Have a cashewnut. - Thank you.
Friends, I have an idea! I have a grand idea!
Since past six years, we are living like loyal dogs!
Like loyal husbands. - Same thing.
We have believed that A stands for apple,
B stands for ball and C stands for cat.
We've also agreed that everyone has a heart.
But our wives have kicked us instead of loving us.
Now we three will go to the college reunion, and that too alone.
And again, we will do A B C D whole heartedly...
so that we get F all day long.
F - F
We will have so much fun...
that the world will be amazed!
That the world will be amazed! - That the world will be amazed!
So, SLUTS, here we come.
Hey guys, are you ready to have fun?
No. - No.
We are ready to have great fun.
What's up guys?
Long time.
Hi guys.
You don't remember my name. - Sorry dear.
No problem. It happens.
Let's play a game.
Okay.
First my wife...
...will give you a hint to her name and you have to guess it.
Then I will give...
What?
Hint. - Yes.
Come on darling, start.
Okay.
Should I wear my name or take it of?
Panty.
What?
Diana Panty.
Her name is Payal.
Her name is Payal. - Oh Payal.
Now my turn.
Shall I give it in the hand or in the mouth?
Your name was not so vulgar.
Prasad.
Oh, Prasad! - Prasad.
Prasad, Panty... I mean Payal...
It's time for our flight.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Sorry.
Excuse me, what is the time?
Bra panties.
I mean... 12:35
Twelve thirty five in english.
Okay honey. - Yes.
Oh no.
Please forgive me sister. - What are you doing?
Leave me. Someone might see us together.
Leave me!
Oh crap!
Rakhi!
Disgusting.
Oh God!
A veil!
Shutter down.
There is no A B or C...
All are walking around holding their D in their hand.
Yes.
Hey, wait.
Why isn't any girl in our college wearing short dresses?
Why are the boys behaving
as though they will be killed if they look at a girl?
Yes.
Because if anyone is caught looking at a girl...
their punishment will be worse than death.
Look there.
That means principal Robert is still the principal here.
Oh crap. - Yes.
Six years ago, a boy named Hardik had inaugurated this tree.
The next day he was admitted to the mental asylum.
I've heard that he is still there.
You mean, the students are still hanged naked on this tree!
No.
Due to the fear of Principal Robert, since last six years...
no student has tried to break his rule.
So no student was required to be tied to this tree.
Since six years this tree has been waiting for its next prey.
No sir, no, please sir, we made a mistake.
And where the offence is, let the great axe fall.
It means,
when required, punishment needs to be administered for wrongs done.
No. - No.
Thank God!
Is Principal Robert on campus today? - No.
He has gone to Yorkshire for three days to attend a conference.
But his loyal soldier is still on-guard.
Look there.
What are you doing?
I'm pulling them out.
What will happen by pulling out plants?
Everything is ruined!
Principal Robert's terror is still ruling over the college.
Rose mam!
She is not Rose mam. She is fully clothed.
She is Rose mam!
Rose mam...
Hello mam. - Rose mam!
Hello.
How are you?
I am fine.
Prem, what are you looking at?
Mam, during our college days,
there was water flowing from this fountain here.
Since last six years all the taps of this college have dried up.
Don't know when there will be drops of water falling all around.
When everything will be wet again.
When will it start raining and everything will be upright.
Prem, let's go to the office and complete the registration.
Yes mam.
Don't know about the statue but Prem's tap is now on.
Wow.
Did you recognize her? - Who?
Marlow!
What are you saying?
Didn't you see her face? - You were looking at her face!
Do you remember, during college days...
Marlow was crazy about you. She wanted you to put...
your straw in her coconut of love and drink from it.
Mangoes ripen but here, coconuts have ripened!
She is sthunning. - Stunning!
Marlow!
Hi.
Meet, I don't believe it. You've changed so much.
You too have changed so much.
Oh you noticed.
Of course! How can I not notice?
It is said that the great wall of China is...
the only wonder that can be seen even from space.
Now two more wonders are added to that list.
How sweet.
How are you?
Fine. - Where is Mrs. Meet?
She is at home. I came alone.
Is it hard, being alone?
Yes it is hard, being alone.
Do you want to get rid of your loneliness?
Yes teacher.
Then report to my private tuitions at 9 o'clock.
I will wait for you.
Yes teacher, yes teacher, yes teacher.
I love my teacher, I love my teacher I love my teacher.
What are you doing now-a-days?
I have two big milk factories.
Milk... factories...
Yes, if you are free tonight at 9,
I will give you a tour of both my factories.
And I will give it to you for free.
What?
Milk. - Milk.
Sure, I will surely drink it. I mean, I will surely come.
Okay, see you at 9.
Bye.
See you.
Yes!
Both of you will get to drive a Ferrari tonight.
But I will still have to ride a hand cart.
Don't worry. You too will find someone.
Yes.
Till then, you celebrate our lottery.
Let's have a beer.
I have beer but don't have an opener.
Shall I open it?
Give it to me.
Take.
Can I help you with something else?
I am Mary, current student of this college.
I have been given the duty to...
...make sure you are properly taken care of.
Amar...
You...
I will need your ID card for registration.
ID card is in my bag.
You take out the ID card. Meanwhile, I will clean the beer.
Okay?
Okay.
It is good that Amar also found a girl.
Yes.
It is not opening.
Just put a little pressure, it will open.
Okay.
She is totally into him!
Go easy. Now slowly take out whatever you want.
Okay.
Hand...
Rope?
Are you also seeing what I am seeing?
Yes.
What is this rope for?
For drying washed clothes.
So long!
Gas chamber!
What is this?
It's a pesticide.
You know how many insects are there in this area?
He's right.
May you get attacked by them!
Umbrella.
Why did you take out the umbrella?
I had packed it with so much effort.
How have you managed to put such big things in such a small place?
This is also an art.
He is a very big artist.
He is not an artist, he is a pervert!
Oh my God! A rat!
Rat.
If you aren't alert,
these rats enter anywhere mistaking it as their home.
But this is dead.
If it enters the wrong place, it will die.
Throw it away.
Rat.
Did you smoke Amar's hookah?
Yes. Did you? - Yes.
Sir, this is not allowed here.
What?
If you get caught, the principal... tree...
Tree...
put it back in.
No, no.
Put it inside.
It is not going inside.
Push it in.
Sorry sir. Did it hurt?
No, I enjoyed it.
Is that so? Then enjoy this.
I can't find what I'm looking for.
Peep inside.
Okay.
Head in the pot.
I got it!
I got the ID card.
Thank God.
Amar keeps his ID card so deep inside?
Let's go, I can't watch it anymore.
What are you doing tonight?
Nothing.
Do you want to play a game?
Game. I love game.
Okay, then see you at 9.
Since when did you become so kinky?
I'm not kinky.
Do you have a backside or a backyard?
She was continuously taking things out of your backside.
She was taking out things from this bag.
Bag!
We were going crazy outside.
We are not going crazy. The girls here are going crazy.
Tonight we will make it rain.
We will. - We will.
And we will blossom three new flowers.
Blossom flowers. - Blossom flowers.
What happened?
I will change and come back.
Darling, when you have to take off your clothes...
what is the point in wearing them?
I will wear such clothes that you will enjoy taking them off.
Come on baby.
African instrument.
Are you naughty boy?
Yes teacher.
Should I punish you?
Yes please, teacher.
Then remove your clothes and stand up on the bed.
Yes. Good teacher. I like my teacher.
I like my teacher.
Tonight, this man will love you with full force.
First, put on man force.
Of course, how can I forget my force?
Use it and enjoy life.
Come on.
Baby...
Are you sure that your parents are not at home?
They are not home. That's why...
It's perfect... superb...
So tell me, who is your daddy?
You are my daddy.
So tell me louder. Who is your daddy?
Oh baby...
Tonight, shall I take you to the moon or stars?
I will be able to decide only after seeing your rocket.
You're in the mood I'm in the mood
There's fire in your attitude baby
There's fire in your attitude dude
Let me invite you as this night is very sexy
In this crazy rain Let's wet our hearts
Come on, let's lock this deal
On the turning of the heart Leave shyness aside
break all the limits and come, my love
Don't tease me like this first please me
by doing something unique, my love
On the turning of the heart Leave shyness aside
break all the limits and come, my love
Don't tease me like this first please me
by doing something unique, my love
Lets take a fun filled ride and Let our hearts get satisfied
Let the love reach new heights Come, let's bet on it
Come on...
Come on, let's lock this deal
You're beautiful, you're elegant
You're a little mean too, oh my love
You're also sly and electrifying
You're excellent, oh my love
You're beautiful, you're elegant
You're a little mean too, oh my love
You're also sly and electrifying
You're excellent, oh my love
You're just like me May this whole world go to heck
Let's do tit for tat in love
Come on, let's lock this deal
You're in the mood I'm in the mood
There's fire in your attitude baby
There's fire in your attitude dude
Let me invite you as this night is very sexy
In this crazy rain Let's wet our hearts
Come on, let's lock this deal
Oh crap! My husband has come.
Husband! - Oh crap!
Oh crap! My brother.
Milkman.
I don't want milk.
Come on baby.
No stupid, my brother.
Oh god! My dad.
Oh baby, this daddy is ever ready.
No stupid! My real dad is here.
Real dad!
Is he your husband? - Yes.
Oh crap.
What?
Why did he have to be your daddy?
Couldn't you find someone else?
You stupid.
Robert is here.
She is Robert Pareira's wife!
He will strip me naked and kill me.
Oh I am already naked.
Is he your brother?
Yes.
Oh crap.
I am dead.
She turned out to be the daughter of this demon.
Oh God!
He will kill me.
He will hang me on the tree.
No, he will put the entire tree up my...
Oh God.
What are you both doing here?
I was going to ask you both the same question.
This is teacher Rose's house.
What?
This is Marlow's house too.
This is Mary's house too.
It means Rose, Mary and Marlow...
are the wife, sister and daughter of Principal Robert.
We came here to do A B C...
now we will get, D for death...
and J for...
We were happy at home. Who asked us to have...
grand fun?
Rose, Mary, Marlow.
Rose,
why weren't you opening the door?
What is this?
Sorry darling, I was in deep sleep.
Yes dad, me too.
Me too, brother.
But you were supposed to come after two days?
How did you come back today?
Why?
Do you have a problem with me coming back soon.
No dad, not at all.
Brother, we are very happy to see you.
I have a feeling that all of you are lying to me.
A lie can be beautifully dressed...
but the truth is always stark naked.
Where are your pants?
I left it in the room. - Oh crap.
So did I. - Oh crap.
Who is it?
Brother, there is no one there.
How is it possible? I just heard some noise.
Brother, What you are looking for?
There is nothing here.
Well, then is it in your room?
No Robert.
Listen carefully...
If you are lying to me then the outcome will be very bad.
Darling, you have to trust us.
I think there is something...
Whom does this pant and t-shirt belong to?
What is going on here?
I don't know whose clothes are these.
I swear on our mother.
No control.
Now you will also say that you don't know whose clothes are these.
Daddy I swear on God, I don't know whose clothes are these.
Rose, you too!
Nanga gang...
Nanga gang!
Yes, these are the clothes of the same gang.
Yes, she is right.
Yes dad, oh my God! That means if you hadn't knocked on the door...
then our lives would've been ruined.
Run.
Who is it?
Nanga gang.
Nanga gang. You fool...
Wait.
Who is it?
Who is it? Stop...
Oh crap. - What happened?
I think my husband has come. Run!
Run.
My pant. - Oh crap! Run!
Run. - Let me at least wear my pants.
Run.
One minute, I'm your husband!
Then why are you asking me to run?
Tell me.
If you are my husband then why are you running out?
Actually...
Run! Death is coming.
Let's catch the first flight home.
Our luggage.
Forget the luggage or we will be dead.
What do you mean?
Run!
Stop!
Let's go. Airport. Go! Go!
Hey! Stop.
Stop! I say stop! Call police!
I haven't done anything and yet I'm in trouble.
You too didn't do anything?
You mean, all three of us haven't done anything.
That means we didn't do anything,
yet now we will have to pay the tax under the principals axe.
But tax is on income...
and in our case there was no in or come.
Hope you haven't left anything in your pants?
Yes I have left.
What? - What?
Condom.
He didn't mean that.
Have you left something like wallet, I card?
Nothing.
Thank God!
What are you listening? Drive faster.
Come. Let's go.
Oh no.
He will kill us.
Yes, he has come here with coffins to take our dead bodies.
Abraham Lincoln has said...
I have always found...
mercy bears richer fruits than strict justice.
It means, forgiveness is greater than punishment.
But they three hadn't celebrated their honeymoon...
in his house, with his family.
If they had, he too would've done the same thing that...
I am going to do with the three of you.
Run!
No! No! - Sir, there is some misunderstanding.
We don't know your wife, sister and daughter.
We don't even know Abraham Lincoln.
We don't even know who John Abraham is.
Yes.
If you are not those three who tried to sleep with my wife, Rose...
daughter Mary and, Sister Marlow...
then what are you doing at the airport at mid-night?
Sir, we are...
Sir. Please.
Please. We haven't done... - Now go and answer to God.
No sir, please forgive us. - We have not done anything.
Darling...
Hi. - Hi.
Yes. We came here to receive our wives.
Darling... - Baby...
Mamta. - Unnati.
Tulsi.
Thank God, you came!
I've never missed you so much.
I would have died without you.
If you hadn't reached on time...
Don't cry. Now we are safe.
Yes.
That's so sweet and romantic.
Who is he?
He is our Principal Robert.
Rose's husband.
Yes.
Mary's father.
Marlow's brother.
Marlow?
Rose? - Mary?
No no Rose, Mary and Marlow.
Whether its Rose, Mary and Marlow...
or Marlow, Rose, Mary...
How does it make a difference?
It's all the same.
Right?
But one second, we came here to give you a surprise.
Then how did you all know that we were coming here today?
How did you know that they were coming?
Sir...
It's my mistake.
How?
Didn't you find out from the credit card company?
I booked our tickets from there.
How else could we have known?
So smart.
Let's go. It's too late...
and we are very screwed.
Not very screwed... very tired.
Let's go.
Good night sir.
Move. Good night.
Let's go.
Oh God.
I left Pappu with my parents.
So that there is no need of heating milk or shaking it.
Nor to put Pappu to sleep.
Tonight, I will play with my husband throughout the night.
Why do you have to tie me up?
I have to. I have seen it on the net.
Let us try something new.
I'll be back.
The train does not have to leave early tonight
as we have the entire night.
I too will board this train. I too have bought a ticket.
Tell the station master to blow the whistle and wave his flag.
Shall I give the signal?
What happened? - What happened?
Nothing. Nothing is going to happen.
Due to engine overload the train has broken down.
It is difficult for it to even stand on the platform.
Let's sleep.
No.
Good night. - No.
Sleep a little away.
Darling, aren't you tired?
Tonight, I am not in the mood of getting tired...
I am in the mood of tiring you.
Darling...
All is well.
Darling, Except this spring, nothing is going to jump up tonight.
Let's sleep.
Good night.
You stupid crow, what are you doing here?
Don't sit on me.
Why you are sitting on me?
Go away.
Don't come up.
You fool!
Don't damage my equipment.
Mom, dad, uncle and neighbours...
What happened, Meet What did the crow do?
Are you hurt?
I'm badly hurt.
In the war between a crow and a parrot, the crow always wins.
Amar Saxena...
Prem Chawla...
Meet Mehta... - What...
Report to my office, immediately.
Meet, why are you walking like this?
Don't ask. That crow broke my eggs.
We can discuss about your eggs later. First, let's meet the principal.
Why has he called us early in the morning?
Yes...
I hope there isn't a new problem.
Come.
You can't go like this.
Put on your clothes.
Okay.
Go quickly.
Today something has happened...
that hasn't happened in last six years.
For the first time, in six years three flowers have bloomed here.
Look at this.
When we did not pour any water...
how did these flowers bloom?
Yes.
Henry David Thoreau had said...
"truth and roses have thorns about them."
It means, truth and flowers, both are filled with thorns.
And these thorns will prick me until...
I find those three gardeners...
who watered these three buds.
Now there is only one solution for my frustration.
Ask me what?
Meditation?
Medication?
Masturbation?
No.
Castration.
I swear on my first wife and Mary's late mother, Laura.
Laura!
Your first wife's name was Laura?
Laura, Rose, Marlow, Mary...
Sir, the names of the women in...
your family sound more like invitations rather than names.
What nonsense?
Sir, I want to ask you something.
How will you find those three people?
Even if they are standing in front of you,
you will not be able to recognize them.
Rose, Mary and Marlow
are like those safes whose locks have been opened.
And thieves come again and again to steal from open safes.
But this time,
I will catch them red-handed and break their keys to pieces.
I specially called you to inform you that...
no one in the campus should find out about what happened last night.
Do you understand boys?
Yes sir. - Okay.
We won't go anywhere near Rose, Mary and Marlow.
What are these women doing with our wives?
Come, let us find out.
Hi. - Hi.
How are you?
Finally, we got the opportunity to meet Rose, Mary and Marlow.
And we realized that we have so much in common.
Too much.
We have become such good friends in just one meeting.
It's like, we are not friends but sisters.
If it is so, then we too have authority over them.
After all, sister-in-law is considered to be like a wife!
Isn't Marlow funny?
I hope her joke does not get us killed.
Marlow is giving us a tour of her milk factory. - Right, right.
Milk? - Do you also want to come?
I have already given him a tour.
He has seen my milk factories very closely.
He has also drank milk there.
Really. - But you never drink milk at home.
No one can resist my factory's milk.
Wow!
Then I too will try.
What? - Bye Meet.
Come on girls, let us go. - Let's go.
Bye boys. - Bye.
Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
Her milk has shaken my brains.
Why have Rose, Mary and Marlow befriend our wives?
It's simple, So that they can be close to us.
That night we started the game but didn't finish it.
They are here to finish it.
Hi. - Hi.
See what we have got from Marlow's factory.
What?
Marlow's milk.
Yes. Isn't it a good tag line?
Drink whenever you want to.
Do you also want to have some?
No, I am not interested in drinking Marlow's milk.
Meet will drink it.
What?
Why will I drink the milk?
No, I will not drink the milk.
Okay, then we will drink it.
Sit.
Come on, let's lock this deal.
I badly need to go to the bathroom.
Ok let's go, even I need to go, come.
Prem, you need to go.
No.
No, I don't have to go.
You have to go, come.
Do I have to go?
I have to go badly.
Let's go.
Darling, we will be back soon.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay.
Come on.
We are doomed. - Yes
Someone has sent me an MMS.
Where I am with Mary and he is with Marlow.
Crap...
Thank God, no one can send me an MMS.
Why?
Because my phone is with my wife.
Why did you hit me?
Your phone is with your wife.
Does that mean that you can't get an MMS?
Yes.
Stop.
Give me this phone. I hate this phone.
People say that an apple a day keeps the doctor away.
But this apple keeps us away from each other.
I phone, I pad and I pod...
because of all these, we don't even require an ***
This phone...
You broke my phone, not yours.
What? - What?
Yes, your phone is in my purse.
Tulsi...
Wait.
You are so right, these phones have become a problem for us.
So, no more phones on this holiday.
Right? - Right.
Do you want to come with me?
Come on. - No, thank you.
Why are you shying away? - Where has this blackmailer called us?
It is the best place to get screwed. - Yes.
You fool...
I can't believe...
that my husband comes to such places for sex.
What can I do darling?
You don't allow me to do anything at home.
It is your mistake.
Did you ever tell me that you are ready to pay me for it.
Come home. We will straighten things out.
Let's go inside.
Yes.
Amar, Meet and Prem...
Boss has asked you to remove your clothes and get cozy in the Jacuzzi.
Clothes. - Cozy in Jacuzzi.
Welcome friends...
Where people come to sin...
you are getting an opportunity to wash away your sins.
You!
Hardik! - It's you!
Not Hardik. These days people call me man with the golden touch.
But weren't you in a mental asylum?
Yes.
Two weeks before, I escaped from there.
To take my six year long revenge
I started keeping an eye on Principal Robert's house.
I was planning to kill him as soon as I get a chance.
But when I saw you three entering...
his house with Rose, Mary and Marlow...
I got an idea.
I realized that some things are more fun...
when you get someone else do them for you.
Will you blackmail your own friends?
We haven't done anything wrong with you?
Yes and why do you need us?
Principal Robert is in college for college re-union the whole day.
You can go there and kill him.
No! I cannot enter the college campus.
The college reminds me of that terrible day.
And weakens the air within me.
What if we refuse to do this?
You will refuse me!
I will show you what will happen.
Look at these videos that I sent to you three.
Shall I send them to the principal?
Please don't do this. - Please don't do this.
Now you all are falling into place.
Just think, if the Principal sees these videos, he will kill you all.
Now the decision is in your hands.
Either kill the principal and save yourselves...
or save the principal and get yourselves killed.
Whom is this soup for?
This is for the principal.
Okay.
Where is the bar?
The counter is right there.
Thank you.
Go and give it.
Where is...?
Sir, this is your special soup.
Okay.
Sorry sir.
I had gone to the soup... I mean loo.
No problem, have a seat.
Why are you staring?
We aren't staring.
Isn't it Prem?
Yes, we are drinking soup.
You too drink your soup.
I don't want to.
It will get cold, sir.
Shut up!
My head is aching.
My entire body is aching.
Hey chicken loli pop,
are you giving me a massage or scratching my head?
Get lost!
You get lost you moron!
You hit me? just wait. - She might know Kung-Fu.
Even I know kung-fu. Come here.
What are you doing? - What do you mean?
We can't do this. We are not murderers.
Shit!
We have to do something to delete the videos from Hardik's phone.
He keeps his phone in his shorts.
We have to do a lot of things to get hold of his phone.
Friends, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
Good evening, sir.
Good evening, Clara.
These are two latest girls.
Bojour! I am Harris from Paris.
I am Shana from Ghana.
And myself secretary.
I'm Bharve.
No D sir, no D.
Bhar...ve. - Bharve.
These two beautiful and delicate girls
have satisfied men all over the world.
But there was no one who could satisfy them.
Do you understand?
From Ghana to Indiana, we demanded a dollar but got a dime.
Whenever we seeked an Eiffel tower we got only a pin.
Don't worry darling.
Very soon, you will be very happy.
Sir, it's your humbleness.
You are such a famous man...
and yet you are taking time out to please them.
Come girls, start sandwich massage.
Okay.
What is the hurry?
First, let us complete what every man desires.
What?
Kiss each other.
What? - What?
Yea.
Kiss each other.
Barve, what is he saying?
Now that sir has made a wish. You both have to fulfill it.
Kiss. - No.
Don't horny me.
Did you enjoy it?
Yes, a lot!
Come on ladies, give me sandwich massage, come on.
Kinky!
Kinky! I love it!
You fool!
You three! - Yes.
What did you think?
You will blackmail us and we will do nothing!
First, we will delete our videos from your phone.
Then we will use the same phone to call the mental asylum
and send you there.
Take out his phone. - Take out.
Why should I take it out?
I won't put my hand in his underwear.
You take it out.
It was your idea. Now you take out the phone.
I will not put my hand in his underwear.
Put your hand.
In his underwear.
Put your hand. - In his underwear.
Okay!
Did you get the phone?
I am still looking for it.
Is there a cave inside, that you are unable to find a phone?
I got it!
Take it out.
that's not the phone.
What?
My hand is stuck!
Take out my hand. - How?
Stop. - Take out my hand.
Stop.
Don't stop.
Pull out my hand. Hurry up!
Otherwise I won't be able to show my hand to anyone!
Video. - Find.
Delete. - Yes.
Delete.
Hello, mental hospital.
Thank God, we got rid of Hardik. - Yes.
What happened, Tulsi? Why are you crying?
Even though I want to, I'm unable to spend time with Prem at home.
I am busy taking care of the entire family...
and not able to give time to my husband.
I can understand.
Since Pappu's birth, it seems as though my love is divided.
I am a good mother but probably not a good wife.
It's Meet and my dream to buy our own home.
A home where we can start our own family.
That's why I work day and night!
But a home is not built with bricks but with emotions.
That's why, I'm a successful boss...
but couldn't be a successful wife.
We came her to re-kindle our love.
But...
Don't worry...
we will not waste any more time to make our husbands happy.
Our wives are not wrong but still they think they are.
And we being wrong aren't rectifying our mistakes.
We can rectify our mistakes by changing ourselves.
Today onwards, we will never stray,
and will never take out the wrong meaning of A B C.
Yes.
I just wish for tonight to pass by peacefully.
We will start a new day tomorrow.
Yes.
And if I ever say "idea" again, then you both slap me.
Idiots.
Not idiots. They are big idiots.
I thought that they will definitely come back to steal from my safes.
But that did not happen...
and tonight is the last night of re-union.
This is the last chance to catch them and...
I will never lose this opportunity.
Kalia...
These are pills that can attract men and women towards each other...
and get them to lose their self-control.
Go and put these pills in the soup.
Good boy.
Good luck.
After drinking this soup...
the three culprits will automatically come to Rose, Mary and Marlow.
And this time they will not be able to get away.
This soup is mind blowing.
It tasting different.
Super cool.
Super hot.
Sexy soup. - Yes.
I'll have one more.
I'll have too.
What a soup!
It's yummy!
Isn't it a yummy soup?
Excellent soup! - Yeah.
Wow.
What an amazing soup!
Something is happening to me.
I am also feeling something.
Me too.
I don't know what but there is something wrong.
I suddenly feel like putting a sticker on my head.
Horny, ok, please, please, please.
It feels like there is a rocket in my pocket.
I feel like having great fun!
I got a rocket in my pocket
O baby come and launch it
So we can fly away now
Get in the room and lock it
I got a rocket in my pocket
O baby come and launch it
So we can fly away now
Get in the room and lock it
Give me a signal of love baby Its 12'o clock in the night
It's time it's time
My heart's engine is running The mercury has risen high
You feel it you feel it.
Give me a signal of love baby Its 12'o clock in the night
My heart's engine is running The mercury has risen high
The kiss of your cheeks is the favorite of lovers,
So let's do it baby do it baby
Do Grand Masti (Grand Fun)
Grand masti Grand masti
Let's do...
Let's do it let's do it say 1-2-3-4
They look just awesome Your tantrums suit you so much
You have completely shaken me Your moves are simply awesome.
Your dance steps are worth millions,
They are like an Air Condition for the eyes...
So let's do it baby do it baby
Do Grand Masti
Grand masti Grand masti
Grand masti
I got a rocket in my pocket
O baby come and launch it
So we can fly away now
Get in the room and lock it
Let's do...
Let's do it let's do it say 1-2-3-4
I will pick and take you away
And make you sit on the bonnet of my heart
Turning the steering of your charisma,
I will press the horn slowly
May there be no speed breaker, Accelerate full on.
So let's do it now do it now
Do Grand Masti
Grand masti Grand masti
Hey you baby
Get on the floor and do the Grand Masti
Grand masti Grand masti
Grand Masti
No, no!
Listen to me.
No, no.
What are you doing? Mary, don't do this.
Mary...
Thank you.
Fools. My doubt was right You are only the three people...
who were behind Rose, Mary and Marlow.
No sir, we didn't do it.
In fact, they were behind us.
Shut up!
Now is not the time to embrace them...
But it's time to embrace your death!
Today, I will reveal your truth and everybody will listen.
You think that you are very important. Right?
But you are not important, you are impotent!
Impotent! - Impotent!
Six years ago he met with an accident.
Since then, his gear is always in neutral.
He hide the truth and tricked me into marrying him...
to show off his manhood to the world.
Then to remove his frustration he scared...
everyone in this college and made them impotent like him.
Rose, What are you saying?
The truth.
So that everyone finds out that
you look fine but there is nothing inside.
Rose is right, brother.
You are my brother, but they all think that I am their sister.
Look at me, papa.
I am grown up now.
I don't want a virgin pinacolada.
I want a cocktail.
Cock... - Enough is enough!
Today, not just the three of us,
but every girl in this college will ask for her right.
We want our right.
We want our right. - We want our right.
Let's go.
Hit him.
What are you doing?
Come on. Let's go.
Bull...
Only this bull can save me from Rose's lust.
Prem, where are you?
Prem, your teacher loves you.
Come to me, my student of the year.
What? Student of the year! Ya right.
Prem...
It got locked?
Help, help, help!
Let me go, old woman.
Darling, where are you?
Come let's play the game.
I am getting suffocated.
I will die due to the heat.
Oh god! Help me, oh god!
Somebody help me.
I'll die!
Open it!
Hole.
The bull with the hole.
Come on.
Meet.
Marlow has jacked me!
Hurry up! The party will start.
I am walking. How much faster can I walk?
Dad, look a buffalo is giving birth to a calf.
Yes, come on.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, come on, you can do it.
Dad look, the buffalo has given birth to a human baby.
Yes son, even when you were born, the doctor said the same thing.
Congratulations!
A buffalo has given birth to a human baby!
Is that so?
No no. - Am I a buffalo?
Listen to me.
Hey aunty...
Oh no.
Let me go.
Where did this old man come from?
Move forward.
Where do I go? Can't you see the old man in front of me?
Mary, today you will be mine!
How disgusting!
Stop.
I will not let you go.
Robert, I will not let you go.
Robert's coming, run!
Run!
Where did they go?
Shit! Dead end!
What do we do now?
Let's get into this building.
Come on.
Prem, at least close the door, lock it.
Good that you three came up.
The distance to reach God has reduced.
No sir. - Please sir.
Good bye boys.
Please help me.
Help! Help!
Shit!
Help.
Help!
You hung me on a tree.
Now see where have I hung you.
Fool...
What are you doing?
Guys, we have to save Principal Robert.
Yes, Prem, Hardik, come, help.
No, why should I save him?
Yes guys, he is right.
If he survives, we three will be dead.
Guys, I know that the principal is not a good man...
and we just found out that he is impotent too.
But still, he is our guru.
Yes.
Hardik, if you save him...
people will not only call you man with a golden touch...
but also man with a golden heart.
Yes.
You are right.
You have opened my eyes.
Come on, let's save Principal Robert.
Yes, come.
Please.
Come.
Come, my children.
I'm dead!
I am saved.
Okay, relax. - I am saved.
Save him.
Okay.
Careful.
Careful, relax.
Careful. - Okay.
Happy journey!
Let me go.
Let me go
Are you here to kill me or save me? Let me go.
I told you not to save him.
Now, we are dead!
Save me.
What did you think?
I will change so easily?
I haven't forgotten that slap.
You had sent me to the mental hospital, right?
You three are crazy.
You three are going to die without even doing anything.
At least you could have had fun with Rose,
Mary and Marlow before dying.
That means, you didn't do anything with Rose, Mary and Marlow.
We have not done anything.
We didn't rob your safes.
Sorry boys, I am really sorry.
So sweet!
All misunderstandings are cleared.
But unfortunately there is only one happy ending to this story.
When you four will die and I will go to Bangkok to celebrate.
Let me go.
Fall! Fall and die!
Fall and die!
Drop him.
Those are Amar, Meet, Prem and brother's voices!
Hello! Who all are hanging there?
You dad is hanging here!
And the whole village is hanging behind him!
Rose! Mary! Marlow!
I am sorry, I am sorry.
Please save us.
How can we save them?
There is no rope or a cable here. How do we save you?
What do we do, sir?
Idea!
Friends, I have an idea!
Unfortunately, I can't slap you in this situation...
but I can still bang into you.
Take this. - Amar what are you doing?
Don't leave my hand!
I have a good idea.
Only one thing can save us from death. Strip!
Strip?
Yes, if Rose, Mary and Marlow take off their clothes...
and make a rope out of it, they can pull us up.
Shut up!
At least before dying you should have given a good idea.
He is right, brother.
We don't have any other idea other than this.
Yes dad, before you lose your grip, we have to strip!
Oh, no!
Oh god! The clothes are not enough.
Robert, the clothes are not enough.
That is why I was telling you not to wear such short dresses.
If you were wearing a saree, you all wouldn't have had to strip!
What do we do now?
Why are you asking us?
Save us!
How?
Do we take off our remaining clothes too?
Yes take them off. - What!
Take them off! - Take them off!
No!
How did all this happen?
Yes, we want to know what happened after the party last night.
Yes.
You have to tell us the truth.
Tell us. - Tell us.
I will tell you.
Because of a misunderstanding between me and Hardik...
we were on the brim of death.
While trying to save us, your husbands also got into trouble.
In fact, you should be proud of them.
They are very nice and good people.
God promise, believe them.
Meet.
How sweet.
Baby.
Excuse me, the visiting hours are over...
all of you, please leave.
Bye honey. - Bye.
Bye darling. - Bye.
Prem - Yes.
What is this?
Nothing, it's just a spring.
It's not a spring boys, it's the thing.
Thing? - Yes.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Mr. Robert.
Because of all these people hanging on you...
there was a lot of pressure on your body and all your veins opened up.
Now the blood is circulating to all the right places.
Congratulations!
You are no more impotent. Have fun my son.
Soon you will be discharged.
Now even I can have great fun with my wife.
Congratulations sir.
Now onwards, we three will also have great fun only..
...with our own wives.
You three will have great fun!
What will I do? Hand fun?
Don't worry my child, I will do something for you.
Your brother has given you to me...
Now I too will give you something.
What?
Wedding ring.
Rose...
I got a rocket in my pocket
O baby come and launch it
So we can fly away now
Get in the room and lock it
I got a rocket in my pocket
O baby come and launch it
So we can fly away now
Get in the room and lock it
Now, I am the only one who is single.
So, if you want to have some fun and play the game with me...
Call me on 929173314.
Let's do it let's do it say 1-2-3-4
Grand masti Grand masti
Your intoxicating like a Margarita
Drinking you gives a different kind of high
Let me invite you as this night is very sexy
In this crazy rain Let's wet our hearts
Come on, let's lock this deal
Give me a signal of love baby Its 12'o clock in the night
My heart's engine is running The mercury has risen high
You feel it you feel it.
You're in the mood I'm in the mood
There's fire in your attitude baby
There's fire in your attitude dude
Your dance steps are worth millions,
They are like an Air Condition for the eyes...
So let's do it baby do it baby
Do Grand Masti
Grand masti Grand masti
O cruel one!
Either give me your heart or kill me
They look just awesome
Your tantrums suit you so much
You have completely shaken me
Your moves are simply awesome.
Your dance steps are worth millions,
They are like an Air Condition for the eyes...
So let's do it baby do it baby
Do Grand Masti
Don't tease me like this first please me
by doing something unique, my love
Grand masti Grand masti
Hey you baby
Get on the floor and do the Grand Masti